<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Classic consoles on Densha de GO! controller documentation</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/classic/</link><description>Recent content in Classic consoles on Densha de GO! controller documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/classic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mamecon (Sony PlayStation)</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/classic/tcpp20002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/classic/tcpp20002/</guid><description>Overview Name Mamecon (Sony PlayStation) Release date March 11, 1999 Serial code TCPP-20002 Notes Supported software (WIP) Software Support Notes BVE Trainsim (PC) Native Requires USB adapter. Supported via input plugin. Densha de GO! (Sony PlayStation 1) Native Densha de GO! 2 Kōsoku-hen (Sony PlayStation 1) Native Densha de GO! 3 Tsūkin-hen (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Densha de GO! Final (Sony PlayStation 2) Unofficial Requires use of cheat codes. Densha de GO!</description></item><item><title>One handle controller (Sony PlayStation)</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/classic/tcpp20001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/classic/tcpp20001/</guid><description>Overview Name One handle controller (Sony PlayStation) Release date March 18, 1999 Serial code TCPP-20001 Notes Supported software (WIP) Software Support Notes BVE Trainsim (PC) Native Requires USB adapter. Supported via input plugin. Densha de GO! (Sony PlayStation 1) Native Densha de GO! 2 Kōsoku-hen (Sony PlayStation 1) Native Densha de GO! 3 Tsūkin-hen (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Densha de GO! Final (Sony PlayStation 2) Unofficial Requires use of cheat codes.</description></item><item><title>Two handle controller (Nintendo 64)</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/classic/tcpp20003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/classic/tcpp20003/</guid><description>Overview Name Two handle controller (Nintendo 64) Release date July 30, 1999 Serial code TCPP-20003 Notes Supported software (WIP) Software Support Notes BVE Trainsim (PC) Native Requires USB adapter. Supported via input plugin. Densha de GO! 64 (Nintendo 64) Native Connect standard controller to P1 and train controller to P3. OpenBVE (PC) Native Requires USB adapter and calibration. Supported via input plugin. Technical details The controller follows the same standard internal operation as other classic controllers.</description></item><item><title>Two handle controller (Sega Dreamcast)</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/classic/tcpp20004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/classic/tcpp20004/</guid><description>Overview Name Two handle controller (Sega Dreamcast) Release date January 20, 2000 Serial code TCPP-20004 Notes Supported software (WIP) Software Support Notes BVE Trainsim (PC) Native Requires USB adapter. Supported via input plugin. Densha de GO! 2 Kōsoku-hen 3000 Bandai (Sega Dreamcast) Native OpenBVE (PC) Native Requires USB adapter and calibration. Supported via input plugin. Technical details The controller follows the same standard internal operation as other classic controllers.</description></item><item><title>Two handle controller (Sega Saturn)</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/classic/tc5175290/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/classic/tc5175290/</guid><description>Overview Name Two handle controller (Sega Saturn) Release date October 1, 1998 Serial code TC-5175290 Notes Supported software (WIP) Software Support Notes BVE Trainsim (PC) Native Requires USB adapter. Supported via input plugin. Densha de GO! EX (Sega Saturn) Native Select controller on game startup. OpenBVE (PC) Native Requires USB adapter and calibration. Supported via input plugin. Technical details The controller follows the same standard internal operation as other classic controllers.</description></item><item><title>Two handle controller (Sony PlayStation)</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/classic/slph00051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/classic/slph00051/</guid><description>Overview Name Two handle controller (Sony PlayStation) Release date December 18, 1997 Serial code SLPH-00051 Notes Also available in golden colour (TCPP-20008). Supported software (WIP) Software Support Notes BVE Trainsim (PC) Native Requires USB adapter. Supported via input plugin. Densha de GO! (Sony PlayStation 1) Native Densha de GO! 2 Kōsoku-hen (Sony PlayStation 1) Native Densha de GO! 3 Tsūkin-hen (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Densha de GO! Final (Sony PlayStation 2) Unofficial Requires use of cheat codes.</description></item><item><title>Classic controllers - Technical details</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/classic/tech/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/classic/tech/</guid><description>Internally, these controllers use the same protocol as a standard controller for the corresponding console and input is reported in the data bytes corresponding to buttons (where each bit reports the state of a single button). Only the regular physical buttons have dedicated bits for them; the handles combine three and four bits for the power notches and brake notches, respectively (you can find an example with the Nintendo 64 here).</description></item></channel></rss>