<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sony PlayStation 2 on Densha de GO! controller documentation</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_ts/ps2/</link><description>Recent content in Sony PlayStation 2 on Densha de GO! controller documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_ts/ps2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Train Simulator Real: THE Yamanote Line</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_ts/ps2/trainyamanote/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_ts/ps2/trainyamanote/</guid><description>Overview Name Train Simulator Real: THE Yamanote Line Japanese name Train Simulator Real THE 山手線 Release date October 4, 2001 Serial code SCPS-15018 Notes Supported controllers Model Support Notes Master Controller (PC) Native Requires official USB adapter. Set to Type F. Master Controller II (PC) Native Requires official USB adapter. Set power to 5 and brake to 8. Multi Train Controller (Sony PlayStation 2) Native P5/B8 cassette. Two handle controller &amp;#34;Type 2&amp;#34; (Sony PlayStation 2) Native</description></item><item><title>Train Simulator Real: THE Keihin Electric Express Railway</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_ts/ps2/trainkeihin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_ts/ps2/trainkeihin/</guid><description>Overview Name Train Simulator Real: THE Keihin Electric Express Railway Japanese name Train Simulator Real THE 京浜急行 Release date October 31, 2002 Serial code SCPS-15035 Notes Supported controllers Model Support Notes Master Controller (PC) Native Requires official USB adapter. Set to Type C. Master Controller II (PC) Native Requires official USB adapter. Set power to 5 and brake to 5. Multi Train Controller (Sony PlayStation 2) Native P5/B5 cassette. Train Mascon (Sony PlayStation 2) Native</description></item><item><title>Train Simulator: Midosuji Line</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_ts/ps2/trainmidosuji/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_ts/ps2/trainmidosuji/</guid><description>Overview Name Train Simulator: Midosuji Line Japanese name Train Simulator 御堂筋線 Release date October 30, 2003 Serial code SLPM-65386 Notes Supported controllers Model Support Notes Master Controller (PC) Native Requires official USB adapter. Set to Type D. Master Controller II (PC) Native Requires official USB adapter. Set power to 4 and brake to 6. Multi Train Controller (Sony PlayStation 2) Native P4/B7 (without B1) cassette.</description></item><item><title>Train Simulator ＋ Densha de GO! Tokyu Line</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_ts/ps2/traindensha/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_ts/ps2/traindensha/</guid><description>Overview Name Train Simulator ＋ Densha de GO!: Tokyu Line Japanese name Train Simulator&amp;#43;電車でGO! 東京急行編 Release date December 18, 2003 Serial code SLPM-65472 Notes Supported controllers Model Support Notes Master Controller (PC) Native Requires official USB adapter. Set to Type D. Master Controller II (PC) Native Requires official USB adapter. Set power to 4 and brake to 5. Multi Train Controller (Sony PlayStation 2) Native P4/B7 cassette. Train Mascon (Sony PlayStation 2) Native</description></item><item><title>Train Simulator: Keisei, Toei Asakusa, Keikyu Lines</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_ts/ps2/trainkeitokei/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_ts/ps2/trainkeitokei/</guid><description>Overview Name Train Simulator: Keisei, Toei Asakusa, Keikyu Lines Japanese name Train Simulator 京成・都営浅草・京急線 Release date August 25, 2005 Serial code SLPM-67007 Notes Supported controllers Model Support Notes Master Controller (PC) Native Requires official USB adapter. Set to Type C. Master Controller II (PC) Native Requires official USB adapter. Set power to 5 and brake to 5. Multi Train Controller (Sony PlayStation 2) Native P5/B5, P13-B7 cassettes. Shinkansen controller (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Train Mascon (Sony PlayStation 2) Native</description></item><item><title>Train Simulator: Kyūshū Shinkansen</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_ts/ps2/trainshinkansen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_ts/ps2/trainshinkansen/</guid><description>Overview Name Train Simulator: Kyūshū Shinkansen Japanese name Train Simulator 九州新幹線 Release date October 1, 2005 Serial code SLPM-67006 Notes Supported controllers Model Support Notes Master Controller (PC) Native Requires official USB adapter. Set to Type G. Master Controller II (PC) Native Requires official USB adapter. Set power to 5 and brake to 7. Multi Train Controller (Sony PlayStation 2) Native P5/B7, P13-B7 cassettes. Shinkansen controller (Sony PlayStation 2) Native</description></item></channel></rss>