<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Adapters and hacks on Densha de GO! controller documentation</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/adapters/</link><description>Recent content in Adapters and hacks on Densha de GO! controller documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/adapters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Converter tool by Autotraintas</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/adapters/autotraintas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/adapters/autotraintas/</guid><description>Autotraintas has created a tool that makes it possible to use nearly any Densha de GO! controller with the PC versions of the games. This includes classic console controllers (USB adapter required) and USB controllers. The tool patches the game memory on the fly to reflect the input from the controller.</description></item><item><title>Input plugins for BVE Trainsim/OpenBVE</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/adapters/plugins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/adapters/plugins/</guid><description>BVE Trainsim and OpenBVE both support input plugins, which allow expanding the controllers compatible with the program.
BVE Trainsim requires installing external input plugins, depending on the controller:
Classic console controllers (電GO PS - JC_PS101Uインターフェイス/電GO PS - JC_PS201Uインターフェイス by saha209, USB adapter required) DGC-255/DGOC-44U/DRC-184 (電GO PCインターフェイス by saha209) TCPP-20009/TCPP-20014/MTC with P5/B8 cassette (電GO PS2インターフェイス by saha209) MTC (other cassettes) (TrainSimulator PS2 MultiTrainController(MTC)インターフェイス by saha209) ZKNS-001 (電GO SWインターフェイス by saha209) OHC-PC01 OpenBVE includes built-in input plugins for all classic and USB Densha de GO!</description></item><item><title>PlayStation 2 cheat codes</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/adapters/cheats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/adapters/cheats/</guid><description>Overview While Densha de GO! 3 and Densha de GO! Shinkansen officially support the original (non-USB) PlayStation controllers, other games are only compatible with USB controllers. Via cheat codes, it is possible to use the original PlayStation controllers on real hardware, either with retail discs or via OPL.
The codes emulate a Type 2 controller. You will need to connect the controller as follows:
Port 1: Dualshock or Dualshock 2 (D-pad, SELECT) Port 2: PlayStation controller (handles and buttons, SELECT is mapped to D) Note Other controllers may be used like this with an adapter (Titan One/Two + Brook/PADEMU).</description></item><item><title>Titan One/Two adapters</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/adapters/titan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/adapters/titan/</guid><description>ConsoleTuner sells the Titan One and Titan Two USB devices. They support scripts to remap buttons or change the behaviour of a controller entirely. There are many repositories available with scripts to make a Densha de GO! controller behave like a different one:
tylau0/DenGo arnauos/densha-de-go mikaeltarquin/densha-de-go thmalex/DenshaDeGoPS1toPS4 MarcRiera/ddgo-scripts Before using a script, check whether it was designed for the Titan One or the Titan Two. They share the same extension (.</description></item></channel></rss>