<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sony PlayStation on Densha de GO! controller documentation</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software/ps1/</link><description>Recent content in Sony PlayStation on Densha de GO! controller documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software/ps1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Densha de GO!</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software/ps1/densha/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software/ps1/densha/</guid><description>Overview Name Densha de GO! Japanese name 電車でGO！ Release date December 18, 1997 Serial code SCPS-45166 Notes Supported controllers Model Support Notes Mamecon (Sony PlayStation) Native One handle controller (Sony PlayStation) Native Two handle controller (Sony PlayStation) Native</description></item><item><title>Densha de GO! 2</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software/ps1/densha2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software/ps1/densha2/</guid><description>Overview Name Densha de GO! 2 Kōsoku-hen Japanese name 電車でGO！2高速編 Release date March 18, 1999 Serial code SLPM-86142 Notes Supported controllers Model Support Notes Mamecon (Sony PlayStation) Native One handle controller (Sony PlayStation) Native Two handle controller (Sony PlayStation) Native</description></item><item><title>Densha de GO! Professional</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software/ps1/pro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software/ps1/pro/</guid><description>Overview Name Densha de GO! Professional Japanese name 電車でGO！プロフェッショナル仕様 Release date December 9, 1999 Serial code SLPM-86378 Notes Supported controllers Model Support Notes Mamecon (Sony PlayStation) Native One handle controller (Sony PlayStation) Native Two handle controller (Sony PlayStation) Native</description></item><item><title>Densha de GO! Nagoya Tetsudōhen</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software/ps1/nagoya/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software/ps1/nagoya/</guid><description>Overview Name Densha de GO! Nagoya Tetsudō-hen Japanese name 電車でGO！名古屋鉄道編 Release date January 27, 2000 Serial code SLPM-86424 Notes Supported controllers Model Support Notes Mamecon (Sony PlayStation) Native One handle controller (Sony PlayStation) Native Two handle controller (Sony PlayStation) Native</description></item><item><title>Kisha de GO!</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software/ps1/kisha/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software/ps1/kisha/</guid><description>Overview Name Kisha de GO! Japanese name 汽車でGO！ Release date March 23, 2000 Serial code SLPM-86449 Notes Supported controllers Model Support Notes Mamecon (Sony PlayStation) Native One handle controller (Sony PlayStation) Native Two handle controller (Sony PlayStation) Native</description></item></channel></rss>