<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>USB on Densha de GO! controller documentation</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/</link><description>Recent content in USB on Densha de GO! controller documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Multi Train Controller (Sony PlayStation 2)</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/sotp031201/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/sotp031201/</guid><description>Overview Name Multi Train Controller (Sony PlayStation 2) Release date December 18, 2003 Serial code SOTP-031201 Notes Released with 4 cartridges: P4-B7, P4-B7 (without B1), P5-B5 and P5-B8. Additional cartridges sold separately: P5-B7 and P13-B7. Supported software (WIP) Software Support Notes BVE Trainsim (PC) Native Supported via input plugin. Densha de GO! 3 Tsūkin-hen (Sony PlayStation 2) Native P5/B8 cartridge. Densha de GO! Final (Sony PlayStation 2) Native P5/B8 cartridge. Densha de GO!</description></item><item><title>One handle controller (Nintendo Switch)</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/zkns001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/zkns001/</guid><description>Overview Name One handle controller (Nintendo Switch) Release date August 5, 2021 Serial code ZKNS-001 Notes Also available as special 1st anniversary translucent exclusive edition (ZKNS-002). Supported software (WIP) Software Support Notes BVE Trainsim (PC) Native Supported via input plugin. Densha de GO! Hashirō Yamanote‑sen (Sony PlayStation 4) Unofficial Requires use of Titan One/Two device. Densha de GO! Hashirō Yamanote‑sen (Nintendo Switch) Native Hmmsim Metro (PC) Native Japanese Rail Sim EX: Nagaragawa Railway (Nintendo Switch) Native Japanese Rail Sim Real Pro: Nagoya Railway (Nintendo Switch) Native Japanese Rail Sim Real Pro: Odakyu Electric Railway (Nintendo Switch) Native Japanese Rail Sim: Akechi Railway (Nintendo Switch) Native Japanese Rail Sim: Journey to Kyoto (Sony PlayStation 4) Unofficial Requires use of Titan One/Two device.</description></item><item><title>One handle controller (PC)</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/dgc255/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/dgc255/</guid><description>Overview Name One handle controller (PC) Release date December 17, 2004 Serial code DGC-255 Notes Supported software (WIP) Software Support Notes BVE Trainsim (PC) Native Supported via input plugin. Densha de GO! (PC) Native Original release requires update. Densha de GO! 2 Kōsoku-hen (PC) Native Original release requires update. Densha de GO! 3 Tsūkin-hen Daiya Kaisei (PC) Native Densha de GO! Final (PC) Native Densha de GO! Nagoya Tetsudō-hen (PC) Native Original release requires update.</description></item><item><title>Ryojōhen controller (PC)</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/dyc288/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/dyc288/</guid><description>Overview Name Ryojōhen controller (PC) Release date June 5, 2003 Serial code DYC-288 Notes Also packaged with serial code DRC-184. Supported software (WIP) Software Support Notes BVE Trainsim (PC) Native Supported via input plugin. Densha de GO! Final (PC) Native Densha de GO! Professional 2 (PC) Native Densha de GO! Ryojōhen (PC) Native OpenBVE (PC) Native Supported via input plugin. Technical details No details are available regarding internal functioning.</description></item><item><title>Ryojōhen controller (Sony PlayStation 2)</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/tcpp20014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/tcpp20014/</guid><description>Overview Name Ryojōhen controller (Sony PlayStation 2) Release date July 25, 2002 Serial code TCPP-20014 Notes Supported software (WIP) Software Support Notes BVE Trainsim (PC) Native Supported via input plugin. Densha de GO! Final (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Densha de GO! Professional 2 (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Densha de GO! Ryojōhen (Sony PlayStation 2) Native OpenBVE (PC) Native Supported via input plugin. Technical details This controller has two handles (4 power notches and an analogue brake handle with three areas), a D-Pad and 7 buttons (Select, Start, Horn, Announce, Camera, Left doors, Right doors).</description></item><item><title>Sangying one handle controller (PC)</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/ohcpc01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/ohcpc01/</guid><description>Overview Name Sangying one handle controller (PC) Release date February 28, 2018 Serial code OHC-PC01 Notes Supported software (WIP) Software Support Notes BVE Trainsim (PC) Native Supported via input plugin. Densha de GO! Hashirō Yamanote‑sen (Nintendo Switch) Unofficial Requires use of Titan One/Two device. Densha de GO! Hashirō Yamanote‑sen (Sony PlayStation 4) Unofficial Requires use of Titan One/Two device. Japanese Rail Sim EX: Nagaragawa Railway (Nintendo Switch) Unofficial Requires use of Titan One/Two device.</description></item><item><title>Shinkansen controller (Sony PlayStation 2)</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/tcpp20011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/tcpp20011/</guid><description>Overview Name Shinkansen controller (Sony PlayStation 2) Release date September 20, 2001 Serial code TCPP-20011 Notes Supported software (WIP) Software Support Notes Densha de GO! Final (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Densha de GO! Professional 2 (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Densha de GO! Ryojōhen (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Densha de GO! Shinkansen San&amp;#39;yō Shinkansen-hen (Sony PlayStation 2) Native OpenBVE (PC) Native Supported via input plugin. Train Simulator: Keisei, Toei Asakusa, Keikyu Lines (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Train Simulator: Kyūshū Shinkansen (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Technical details This controller has two handles (13 power notches and 7+emergency brake notches), a D-Pad and 6 buttons (Select, Start, A, B, C, D).</description></item><item><title>Train Mascon (Sony PlayStation 2)</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/cotm02001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/cotm02001/</guid><description>Overview Name Train Mascon (Sony PlayStation 2) Release date October 31, 2002 Serial code COTM-02001 Notes Supported software (WIP) Software Support Notes Train Simulator &amp;#43; Densha de GO!: Tokyu Line (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Train Simulator Real: THE Keihin Electric Express Railway (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Train Simulator: Keisei, Toei Asakusa, Keikyu Lines (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Train Simulator: Midosuji Line (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Technical details This controller has one handle (5 power notches and 8+emergency brake notches), a D-Pad and 7 buttons (Select, Start, A, B, C, Close, ATS).</description></item><item><title>Two handle controller "Type 2" (Sony PlayStation 2)</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/tcpp20009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/tcpp20009/</guid><description>Overview Name Two handle controller &amp;#34;Type 2&amp;#34; (Sony PlayStation 2) Release date March 15, 2001 Serial code TCPP-20009 Notes Also available in purple skeleton colour (TCPP-20012). Supported software (WIP) Software Support Notes BVE Trainsim (PC) Native Supported via input plugin. Densha de GO! 3 Tsūkin-hen (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Densha de GO! Final (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Densha de GO! Professional 2 (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Densha de GO! Ryojōhen (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Densha de GO!</description></item><item><title>Two handle controller (PC)</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/dgoc44u/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/controllers/usb/dgoc44u/</guid><description>Overview Name Two handle controller (PC) Release date June 15, 2001 Serial code DGOC-44U Notes Supported software (WIP) Software Support Notes BVE Trainsim (PC) Native Supported via input plugin. Densha de GO! (PC) Native Original release requires update. Densha de GO! 2 Kōsoku-hen (PC) Native Original release requires update. Densha de GO! 3 Tsūkin-hen Daiya Kaisei (PC) Native Densha de GO! Final (PC) Native Densha de GO! Hashirō Yamanote‑sen (Sony PlayStation 4) Unofficial Requires use of Titan One/Two device.</description></item></channel></rss>