<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PC on Densha de GO! controller documentation</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_other/pc/</link><description>Recent content in PC on Densha de GO! controller documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_other/pc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BVE Trainsim</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_other/pc/bve/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_other/pc/bve/</guid><description>Overview Name BVE Trainsim Release date September 5, 2011 Website https://bvets.net/en/ Notes Compatibility applies to version 5 or later. Supported controllers Model Support Notes Mamecon (Sony PlayStation) Native Requires USB adapter. Supported via input plugin. Multi Train Controller (Sony PlayStation 2) Native Supported via input plugin. One handle controller (Nintendo Switch) Native Supported via input plugin. One handle controller (PC) Native Supported via input plugin. One handle controller (Sony PlayStation) Native Requires USB adapter.</description></item><item><title>OpenBVE</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_other/pc/openbve/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_other/pc/openbve/</guid><description>Overview Name OpenBVE Release date March 23, 2009 Website https://openbve-project.net/ Notes Controllers are supported on version 1.8.2.0 or later via built-in input plugins. Supported controllers Model Support Notes Mamecon (Sony PlayStation) Native Requires USB adapter and calibration. Supported via input plugin. Multi Train Controller (Sony PlayStation 2) Partial Only P5/B8 cassette. Supported via input plugin. One handle controller (Nintendo Switch) Native Supported via input plugin. One handle controller (PC) Native Supported via input plugin.</description></item><item><title>Train Crew</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_other/pc/traincrew/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/software_other/pc/traincrew/</guid><description>Overview Name Train Crew Release date September 30, 2021 Website https://acty-soft.com/traincrew/ Notes Supported controllers Model Support Notes Two handle controller (PC) Unofficial Requires use of Titan One/Two device. One handle controller (Nintendo Switch) Native Sangying one handle controller (PC) Native</description></item></channel></rss>