<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Models on Densha de GO! controller documentation</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/models/</link><description>Recent content in Models on Densha de GO! controller documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/models/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Classic consoles</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/models/classic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/models/classic/</guid><description>The information in this section applies to the following controllers:
SLPH-00051: two-handle controller (Sony PlayStation) TC-5175290: two-handle controller (Sega Saturn) TCPP-20001: single-handle controller (Sony PlayStation) TCPP-20002: gamepad controller (Sony PlayStation) TCPP-20003: two-handle controller (Nintendo 64) TCPP-20004: two-handle controller (Sega Dreamcast) TCPP-20008: two-handle controller, golden (Sony PlayStation) These controllers all have five physical buttons (SELECT, START, A, B, C) and two handles (with the TCPP-20001 combining them into one). Internally, they use the same protocol as a standard controller for the corresponding console and input is reported in the data bytes corresponding to buttons (where each bit reports the state of a single button).</description></item><item><title>Serial port</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/models/serial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/models/serial/</guid><description>The information in this section applies to the following controllers:
DGOC-44: two-handle controller (Microsoft Windows) This is the original controller for the Microsoft Windows releases. No details are available regarding internal functioning.</description></item><item><title>USB</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/models/usb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/models/usb/</guid><description>The information in this section applies to the following controllers:
DGC-255: one-handle controller (Microsoft Windows) DGOC-44U: two-handle controller (Microsoft Windows) DRC-184/DYC-288: Ryojōhen controller (Microsoft Windows) TCPP-20009: two-handle controller &amp;ldquo;Type 2&amp;rdquo; (Sony PlayStation 2) TCPP-20011: Shinkansen controller (Sony PlayStation 2) TCPP-20012: two-handle controller &amp;ldquo;Type 2&amp;rdquo;, purple skeleton (Sony PlayStation 2) TCPP-20014: Ryojōhen controller (Sony PlayStation 2) MTC: Multi Train Controller (Sony PlayStation 2) ZKNS-001: one-handle controller (Nintendo Switch) DGC-255 This controller has one handle (5 power notches and 8+emergency brake notches), a D-Pad and 6 buttons (Select, Start, A, B, C, D).</description></item><item><title>Nintendo Wii</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/models/wii/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/models/wii/</guid><description>The information in this section applies to the following controllers:
TCPP-20017: Shinkansen controller This controller is similar externally to the PlayStation 2 version of the Shinkansen controller. However, the screen has been replaced by a sticker and there is no pedal, so the only functioning parts are the handles, the buttons and the door lamp. In addition, instead of USB, it connects to a Wiimote using its extension port, like other accessories made for the console.</description></item><item><title>Standalone</title><link>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/models/standalone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcriera.github.io/ddgo-controller-docs/models/standalone/</guid><description>The information in this section applies to the following controllers:
Densha de GO! Plug and Play This controller is different from traditional controllers in the sense that it contains the game (an improved version of Densha de GO! Final) and does not connect to a PC or console. Externally, it looks similar to a TCPP-20009, except it does not include a pedal connection. Internally, it contains an ARM board running Linux.</description></item></channel></rss>